Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES, 1921-80 (Part 2)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES (part 2)
  - FPIA, Agency for International Development
    - Grant Aid/csd- 3289
      - Evaluation Team, 11/20/1972-1/15/1973 (Box 83, Folder 59)
      - Implementation Plan for Improvements in the Program Operations of Grant Aid, 4/27/1972 (Box 83, Folder 60)
      - Proposal for the Second Evaluation of Grant Aid/csd-3289, 9/1974-10/7/1974 (Box 83, Folder 61)
      - A Request for an Amendment for Fiscal Year 1973, 1/25/1973 (Box 83, Folder 62)
    - Hilltribes Project (Voluntary Sterilization), 3/28/1977-6/10/1977 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Indirect Cost Rate Negotiations, 3/6/1978 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - FPIA
    - Asia Foundation, 3/7/1977-5/23/1977 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Association for Voluntary Sterilization, 6/1/1972-12/7/1972 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Berkowitz, Dr. Richard, Consultant, 5/9/1973-8/10/1973 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Brochures, 6/6/1974 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Church World Service, FPIA Agreement Between FPIA and CWS Legal, (Paul, E.), 1/31/1979 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Church World Service, Correspondence from 1971
      - 1971-1974 (Box 84, Folder 8)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 84)
    - Church World Services, FPIA Memo of Understanding Between FPIA and Material Resources Program CWS (Revision), 11/22/1977 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Colorado Population Course, PPFA-FPIA-UCMC-1, 4/21/1972-7/5/1974 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Family Planning Training for Physicians Who Will Work Overseas, PPFA-FPIA-UCMC-1, 6/30/1972 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Colorado Population Course, FPIA Summary, Evaluation Justification for Refunding PPFA-FPIA-UCMC-1 1973, 5/3/1973-5/8/1973 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Commodities
      - 1973-1974 (Box 84, Folder 13)
      - 1976-1978 (Box 84)
    - Commodities Procurement and Distribution Manual, 9/26/1975 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Contraceptive Distribution (Restrictions), 12/8/1971-2/11/1972 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Criteria for Determination of Management and Program Dollar Costs, 1/28/1974-8/8/1974 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - The Dalkon Shield, 6/3-13/1974 (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - Descriptive List of Available Commodities, circa 1973 (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - East-West Communication Institute, 3/15/1973-5/31/1973 (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - Educational Materials Review Committee, Minutes, 2/17/1972-6/8/1972 (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - An Evaluation of the STCSS from 1974-1978, Part I, The Training Program, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - An Evaluation of the STCSS, Part II, Profile of the Acceptors from 1974-1978, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Executive Talent Search, 8/9-10/1971 (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - Fact Sheet, 11/18/1977 (Box 84, Folder 24)
    - Film Agreement, Buena Vista International, 5/5/1975-8/8/1975 (Box 84, Folder 25)
    - Film Agreement, Walt Disney Educational Media Company, 6/4/1975-8/12/1975 (Box 84, Folder 26)
    - The First Four Years, 9/10/1975 (Box 84, Folder 27)
    - Materials Survey, 5/12/1977 (Box 84, Folder 28)
    - Medical Standards, 10/15/1973-1/28/1974 (Box 84, Folder 29)
    - Program Present at PPFA Board of Directors Meeting, 5/31/1974-6/1/1974 (Box 84, Folder 30)
    - Procurement and Distribution, 5/10/1973-9/6/1973 (Box 84, Folder 31)
    - Steering Committee, 5/4/1973-9/6/1973 (Box 84, Folder 32)
    - General Correspondence, 2/22/1978-12/28/1979 (Box 84, Folder 33)
    - General Correspondence from 1971
      - 1971-1973 (Box 84, Folder 34)
      - 1975, 1977 (Box 84)
    - General, 3/10/1978 (Box 84, Folder 35)
    - General Role, Services, Future, 1976 (Box 84, Folder 36)
    - General Services Administration, 9/28/1976 (Box 84, Folder 37)
    - Grants from FPIA, Attachments B and C, 9/1/1974 (Box 84, Folder 38)
    - HEW Contract 240-75-0104 (Fund 4075) (Mary McGovern), 2/9/1978-2/14/1978 (Box 84, Folder 39)
    - HEW Contract #HSA-105-74-198 (McGovern), 10/22/1975-10/6/1976 (Box 84, Folder 40)
    - Hospitals, Correspondence, 8/19/1971-5/18/1973 (Box 84, Folder 41)
    - The Human Life Foundation from 1973
      - 1973-1974 (Box 84, Folder 42)
      - 1975 (Box 84)
    - Insurance Coverage, 7/31/1975-2/14/1979 (Box 84, Folder 43)
    - International Educational Development from 1972-1973
      - 1972-1973 (Box 84, Folder 44)
      - 1975 (Box 84)
    - International Family Planning Digest, 2/1975-9/1976 (Box 84, Folder 45)
    - Newsletter Vol.5 1&2, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 46)
    - IPPF from 1971
      - 1971-1974 (Box 84, Folder 47)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 84)
    - Job Applicants, 7/20/1971-8/8/1973 (Box 84, Folder 48)
    - Job Descriptions from 1971
      - 1971 (Box 84, Folder 49)
      - 1975 (Box 84)
    - List of Church-Related Hospitals Known to Provide Family Planning Services, 8/31/1971 (Box 84, Folder 50)
    - Medical Guidelines, 12/11/1975 (Box 84, Folder 51)
    - Medical Standards of FPIA
      - 1973-1974 (Box 84, Folder 52)
      - 1975 (Box 84)
    - Meharry Medical College, 4/4/1972-1/19/1973 (Box 84, Folder 53)
    - General memos, mimeos, from 1971
      - 1971-1974 (Box 84, Folder 54)
      - 1977 (Box 84)
    - Monthly Activity Profile, 2/1977-1/1978 (Box 84, Folder 55)
    - Monthly Summary of Grantee Financial Position (Selected Grantees) and Transactions, 2/11/1977-3/31/1977 (Box 84, Folder 56)
    - Organization Chart, 1/7/1974-11/12/1974 (Box 84, Folder 57)
    - Personnel, Vacations, Leaves, Change of Status, Terminations, Etc., 12/15/1971-7/19/1973 (Box 84, Folder 58)
    - Personnel Policies Regional Office Staff, 1/4/1977-12/15/1977 (Box 84, Folder 59)
    - Priority List, 7/24/1973 (Box 84, Folder 60)
    - Program Year 4 Projects, circa 1974 (Box 84, Folder 61)
    - Projects Assigned to Family Planning Services Unit of FPIA, 8/10/1973-9/5/1973 (Box 84, Folder 62)
    - Project Proposals from 1974
      - 1974 (Box 84, Folder 63)
      - 1975-1976, 1978 (Box 84)
    - First Year Activities: A Preliminary Report and Work Plan for Fiscal Year 1973, 3/31/1972 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Second Annual Report, 3/31/1973 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Grant Aid/csd 3289 Report of Evaluation Team FPIA, 3/30/1973 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report for Program Year 3, Proposal for Program Year 4, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report for Program Year 4, Proposal for Program Year 5, 1975 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Report of the Evaluation of Family Planning International Assistance, 1975 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Grant Aid/csd 3289 FPIA report of Evaluation Volume Two: Reports of Project Site Visits, 1975 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Family Planning International Assistance The First Four Years (Final Report for Grant No. AID/CSD-3289), 7/1975 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report Year 7, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Draft Report of the FPIA to the June 1972 Meeting of the Board of Directors, 5/8/1972 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Reports, The First Seven Years, 10/1978 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Activities Reports, 9/1/1978-10/17/1979 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Report of Project Activities to Date and Work Plans for Jan.-June 1972, 11/20/1971 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Reports, Family Planning Services in Africa, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Africa Regional Report (Robinson), 3/4/1975 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Project Reports, Robinson, 10/17/1972-5/21/1973 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Report/Programming Trip to Ghana/Christian Council of Ghana, Robinson, 11/30/1972-12/7/1972 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Asia Field Reports (Dr. Derman), 9/12/1973 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Reports, Follow-Up Study of Oral Contraceptive Acceptors in Howrah District, India, 10/28/1974 (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Goals and Activities Report to June 30,1972, 1/1972 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Report on the Pilot Survey of Church-Related Hospitals (Jan-June,1972), 10/31/1972-11/14/1972 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Report to the National Executive Committee, 1/20/72 (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Status Report, A Report to the National Executive Committee, 1/20/1972 (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - Summary Program Report, 10/1973 (Box 85, Folder 24)
    - Trip Report, Drexler, Anthony, 9/8/1975 (Box 85, Folder 25)
    - Field Trip Report, Anthony Drexler, 3/26/1974-12/12/1974 (Box 85, Folder 26)
    - Review of FPIA's Management and Project Support Functions, 1/27/1975 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Review of FPIA Planning, Approval and Implementation of Project Grant Assistance, 4/18/1972-5/5/1972 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Trip Report to Colombia, J.C.Robbins, 11/26/1973-12/12/1973 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Research Programs, 2/24/1972-6/16/1972 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Semi-Annual Meeting, 9/11/1975-9/29/1975 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Special Projects, 3/27/1972 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - State University of NY, Downstate Medical Center, Family Planning, Nurse, Midwife, 5/15/1973-5/18/1973 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Sterilization, 8/24/1976-1/11/1978 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Institutional Survey, Preliminary Report, Varky, 8/10/1973-8/21/1973 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Success Stories, 8/18/1975-8/26/1975 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Surveys, 9/18/1972 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Unit Heads Meeting, 8/8/1973-12/7/1973 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - University of Illinois, Training System Computer-Based Ed. Research Lab., 5/11/1972 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - University of Hawaii PP Hawaii, 8/7/1972-12/13/1973 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Werkman, Sidney, MD, Univ. of Colorado, Application, African Employment, not approved. Summary Statement, 2/24/1976-5/4/1976 (Box 86)
    - What it is. What it does, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Trip Report, MWIA Conference, Manila, Derman, R.J., MD, 1/28/1974 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - STAFF
    - Arnold, Elizabeth
      - Correspondence and Memos, 4/17/1973 (Box 86, Folder 18)
      - Nurses-Midwifes, General, miscellaneous, circa 1973 (Box 86, Folder 19)
      - Nurse-Midwife Training Courses, 4/12/1973 (Box 86, Folder 20)
      - Chronological, 4/11/1973-5/29/1973 (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - Carlo, Jose
      - Director Information, Education and Communications, 11/26/1974 (Box 86, Folder 22)
      - Chronological, 8/23/1973-8/24/1973 (Box 86, Folder 23)
    - Crow, Harold
      - Director of Family Planning Services, 3/12/1973-9/20/1974 (Box 86, Folder 24)
      - Chronological from February, 2/18/1972-4/25/1974 (Box 86, Folder 25)
    - Derman, Richard MD, Director, 9/25/1975-7/1/1976 (Box 86, Folder 26)
    - Drexler, Anthony E., Chronological, 8/20/1973-4/26/1974 (Box 86, Folder 27)
    - Groot, Hans C., Chronological from March, 3/14/1973-7/31/1973 (Box 86, Folder 28)
    - Johnson, Bonnie, Training Specialist
      - Correspondence and Memos, 1/5/1973-2/28/1973 (Box 86, Folder 29)
      - Chronological, 10/10/1972-5/15/1973 (Box 86, Folder 30)
    - Lee, Yoh OK, Chronological, 2/15/1972-7/23/1973 (Box 86, Folder 31)
    - Lorenza, Carrie
      - Field Representative, Asia
        - 1973-1974 (Box 86, Folder 32)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 86)
      - Chronological, 7/20/1971-2/1/1972 (Box 86, Folder 33)
    - Mathai, John, Correspondence and Memos, 7/29/1976-7/30/1976 (Box 86, Folder 34)
    - Parker, David, Field Rep., Latin America
      - 1974 (Box 86, Folder 35)
      - 1976 (Box 86)
    - Patterson, Charles, Chronological, 11/19/1971-4/10/1973 (Box 86, Folder 36)
    - Perez, Edward L, Chronological, 1971-1973 (Box 86, Folder 37-38)
    - Robinson, Leonard
      - Correspondence and Memos
        - 1972-1974 (Box 86, Folder 39)
        - 1977 (Box 86)
      - Chronological, 7/5/1972-11/28/1973 (Box 86, Folder 40)
    - Smith, John Palmer
      - Staff Appointments, Nonprofessional, 7/13/1972-7/31/1972 (Box 86, Folder 41)
      - Correspondence, 7/16/1971-4/16/1973 (Box 86, Folder 42)
      - Memos from 1971
        - 1971-1974 (Box 86, Folder 43)
        - 1975 (Box 86)
      - Professional Staff Appointments, 8/11/1971-9/1/1972 (Box 86, Folder 44)
      - Chronological, 1971-1974 (Box 86, Folder 45-48)
    - Varky, George, Correspondence and Memos, 6/8/1976-8/18/1976 (Box 86, Folder 49)
    - Encuesta Institucional de FPIA 1972-1973 Infrome Preliminar, George Varky, 8/10/1973 (Box 86, Folder 50)
    - Varky, George
      - A Family Planning Model, 9/16/1975 (Box 86, Folder 51)
      - Many Families/One Family: What Shall We Say to Our Children?, 5/1974 (Box 86, Folder 52)
    - Vice President for International Programs, Weintraub, Daniel
      - Appointment 1/27/78, 1/30/1978-10/17/1978 (Box 86, Folder 53)
      - Correspondence and Memos, 9/15/1975-2/1/1978 (Box 86, Folder 54)
      - Memo of Understanding FPIA and Organizations that Receive Contraceptive Commodity Assistance, 7/24/1975-9/5/1975 (Box 86, Folder 55)
    - Wiley, Andrew T. MD
      - Correspondence and Memos from 1973
        - 1972-1973 (Box 86, Folder 56)
        - 1978 (Box 86)
      - Chronological, 4/10/1973-5/11/1973 (Box 86, Folder 57)
    - Misc. Staff, Chronological, 7/11/1972-10/19/1973 (Box 86, Folder 58)
    - Project Proposals, 4/12/1972-12/18/1973 (Box 86, Folder 59)
    - Project Proposal Checklist, 2/15/1979 (Box 86, Folder 60)
    - Project No. Date Amount Grantee Project Title, circa 1975 (Box 86, Folder 61)
    - Project Rating System from 1974-1975
      - 1974 (Box 86, Folder 62)
      - 1975 (Box 86)
    - Proposal, "Advances In Planned Parenthood" [APPP], 8/27/1973-2/25/1974 (Box 86, Folder 63)
    - Proposed Project Rating System, Varky, George, 10/22/1973 (Box 86, Folder 64)
    - Proposal for Funding Information, Education and Communications, 4/1/1971-11/30/1971 (Box 86, Folder 65)
    - Proposal for International Family Planning Institute, 6/9/1972 (Box 86, Folder 66)
    - Questionnaires, circa 1972 (Box 86, Folder 67)
    - Regional Budgets, 4/1/1977-10/8/1979 (Box 86, Folder 68)
    - Requests for Funding from FPIA, 7/25/1972-8/15/1972 (Box 86, Folder 69)
    - Reorganization of Management, 4/14/1975-5/28/1975 (Box 86, Folder 70)
  - International Planned Parenthood Federation
    - Annual Reports, from 1952
      - 1952-1968 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - 1975, 1977 (Box 87)
    - Annual Report Questionnaires, 4/8/1974 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Robbins, Annual Report, 4/16/1974-5/8/1974 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Budget, 9/23/1966-7/18/1967 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Audits and Budgets, 11/26/1963-12/31/1971 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Central Office Reorganization, 5/11/1976 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee Meetings, 1/9/1964-5/7/1974 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Budget Committee, 12/31/1970-7/17/1972 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Finance Committee, 10/1969-2/5/1970 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Management and Planning Committee Minutes, Miscellaneous, 9/11/1970-4/22/1974 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Meetings, Management, and Planning, Miscellaneous, from 1963 Minutes - Reports, 2/1964-11/1967 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Management and Planning Committee Program to Expedite World Fertility Control, 3/1962-6/1962 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Proposed Restructuring of the Committee Structure, 11/17/1975 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - England Medical Committee, Handbook, circa 1968 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Medical Dept., Oral Contraceptives, 12/19/1969-4/1973 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Medical Sub-Committee, Tests, U.S. Products, 12/20/1960-5/24/1969 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, England, 7/7/1970-11/30/1970 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, England, 1/23/1976-10/18/1979 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, England, 1971-1974 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Africa, I&E Program from 1972
      - 1972-1974 (Box 88, Folder 13)
      - 1975 (Box 88)
    - Allocations Committee, John Robbins, 3/4/1974-11/20/1974 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Allocations Committee, Minutes, 1/19/1973-4/24/1974 (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Approximation Study, Status of Family Planning, Robbins, 11/4/1971-10/5/1973 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Robbins, Appleweig Report, Oral Contraceptive Shortage, 5/30/1974-6/12/1974 (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Robbins, J., Applications for Membership (Associate) In IPPF, 3/2/1971 (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Budget, John Robbins, 12/21/1973 (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - John Robbins, Cash Flow to IPPF, January 1969 to December 1974, circa 1975 (Box 88, Folder 20)
    - John Robbins, Cash Flow to IPPF, June 1968 to June 1974 - six months ending, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 21)
    - Robins, Caspar Brooks "An Important Future", 11/1973-5/7/1973 (Box 88, Folder 22)
    - Robbins, Carl Djerassi, Fertility Control in China, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 23)
    - John C. Robbins, Correspondence from 1974
      - 1974 (Box 88, Folder 24)
      - 1975 (Box 88)
    - Dr. Malcolm Potts, Correspondence, Robbins, 1/11/1973-10/30/1974 (Box 88, Folder 25)
    - John C. Robbins, Correspondence, 1/27/1972-5/30/1973 (Box 88, Folder 26)
    - Robbins, Cost/Benefit Study, Brazil, 2/12/1973-5/30/1973 (Box 88, Folder 27)
    - Robbins, Evaluation Questionnaire, 21st Anniversary Conference Brighton, 1/27/1974-2/15/1974 (Box 88, Folder 28)
    - Robbins, Gifts Other Than Victor Bostrom, Restricted to IPPF, 3/4/1974-3/12/1974 (Box 88, Folder 29)
    - Robbins, History IPPF - PPFA, Victor Bostrom Fund Raising, 1961-1975, 1975 (Box 88, Folder 30)
    - Robbins, J.C., Management and Planning Committee from 1974
      - 1974 (Box 88, Folder 31)
      - 1975 (Box 88)
    - Abel-Smith, Brian, The General Rapporteurs Report, Brighton Conference, 10/27/1973 (Box 88, Folder 32)
    - Berelson, Bernard: PP Reconsidered, Speech at Brighton Conference, 10/1973 (Box 88, Folder 33)
    - John Robbins, OECD, 2/26/1974-7/2/1974 (Box 88, Folder 34)
    - Robbins, Pill Distribution Project in Brazil (Rio Grande de Norte), 4/27/1973-9/25/1973 (Box 88, Folder 35)
    - John Robbins, Proposal for Method for Rational Allocation of Funds, FP Association, 1/1974-4/10/1974 (Box 88, Folder 36)
    - John Robbins, Proposal, The Promotion of Change, Confidential, 8/1974-10/15/1974 (Box 88, Folder 37)
    - Robbins, IPPF 21st Anniversary Conference, Brighton, 4/18/1973-3/20/1974 (Box 88, Folder 38)
    - Robbins, Survey of World Needs and Family Planning, 1/1975 (Box 88, Folder 39)
    - Robbins, Summary of Funds Available to Grant, Receiving FPAS, 1/10/1975 (Box 88, Folder 40)
    - "Twin Cities" Campaign, IPPF/PPFA, 1/12/1973-3/26/1973 (Box 88, Folder 41)
    - Formula IPPF-PPFA Financial Arrangements, 1/14/1976-10/30/1978 (Box 88, Folder 42)
    - Founders Research Awards, 11/15/1974 (Box 88, Folder 43)
    - Grant no. AID/csd-1837, Status Report as of Dec. 31, 1967, 3/10/1968 (Box 88, Folder 44)
    - Governing Body Meeting, 10/31/1973-11/2/1973 (Box 88, Folder 45)
    - Income to IPPF, 3/24/1975 (Box 88, Folder 46)
    - "International Secretariat", Feasibility Study, 9/16/1975 (Box 88, Folder 47)
    - International Information Program, (PPWP -IPPF), 10/31/1966-10/25/1967 (Box 88, Folder 48)
    - IPPF-PPFA Financial Agreement
      - 1961-1973 (Box 88, Folder 49)
      - 1975 (Box 88)
    - Lists, Events, Reports from 1970
      - 1971-1974 (Box 88, Folder 50)
      - 1975 (Box 88)
    - Lists, Events, Reports, 9/16/1959-9/18/1969 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Julia Henderson's Visit to U.S.A., 8/1/1972-10/26/1972 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Minutes of Central Council (Policy Statements), Nov. 17-19, 1978, 1/1979 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Oxfam Projects, 10/1965-9/1966 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Dr. Malcolm Potts' Visit to U.S., 1/29/1971-5/27/1971 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Draft Report of the Study of IPPF and its Future, 8/1977 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Report of Working Party on Audio-Visual Communication, 2/21/1977-2/24/1977, 2/16/1978 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - England Medical Comm., Miscellaneous and Memos, 10/1959-10/1971 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - AID, 5/10/1967-12/7/1971 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - News Releases, 9/1961-10/1972 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Programme Review and Financial Statements, 1975-1976 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Bio-Medical Research Stimulation Project, 6/1/1973 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Victor Fund, Victor Bostrom Fund, Spring 1967-7/26/1973 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Victor Bostrom Fund, Committee Membership, n.d. (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - World Lists, Family Planning Agencies from 1959
      - 1957-1970 (Box 89, Folder 15)
      - 1976 (Box 89)
    - Work Programme for the Period, 1972-1974, 1/1972 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Review of Family Planning Practices and Services, 1971-1973, 11/1/74 (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Simple Methods of Distributing Family Planning Supplies, Lubin, Potts, Griffith, 5/22/1973 (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Survey: Legal Approach to Family Planning of Member Organizations, 9/30/1970 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - John Robbins, Unmet Needs Study from 1973
      - 1973-1974 (Box 89, Folder 20)
      - 1975 (Box 89)
    - Unmet Needs Study 1973 (empty file) (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - Master Copy: Unmet Needs Study, 9/1973 (Box 89, Folder 22)
    - World Population Year 1974, 6/3/1974 (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - Western Hemisphere Region, AID, 1/1968-2/1968 (Box 89, Folder 24)
    - Western Hemisphere Audits, Budgets, By-laws, 9/23/1964-4/1967 (Box 89, Folder 25)
    - Western Hemisphere Region
      - Establishment of Medical Committee, Bogota, Colombia, May 8,1968, 6/25/1969 (Box 89, Folder 26)
      - Executive Committee, Minutes, Miscellaneous, 11/18/1970-6/15/1973 (Box 89, Folder 27)
      - Grants, Committee, Minutes, Miscellaneous, 12/15/1971-9/27/1973 (Box 89, Folder 28)
      - Medical Committee, Official Stand on Non-Clinical Distribution of Oral Contraceptives, n.d. (Box 89, Folder 29)
      - Medical Committee, Oral Contraceptives, 12/11/1969 (Box 89, Folder 30)
      - Contributions, Temporary Folder, 1/13/1976 (Box 89, Folder 31)
      - Allocation Committee, Minutes, Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 4/24/1969-12/8/1972 (Box 89, Folder 32)
      - Statistics, 5/8/1979-12/21/1979 (Box 89, Folder 33)
      - 1970-1974 (Box 89, Folder 34)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 89)
      - [Correspondence], 1958-1969 (Box 89, Folder 35-38)
      - J.C. Robbins, Correspondence from 1972
        - 1972-1974 (Box 90, Folder 1)
        - 1975 (Box 90)
      - John C. Robbins, Correspondence, 6/7/1971 (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - Changing Attitudes in U.S. Towards Abortion and Voluntary Sterilization, J.C.R., 12/10/1970-12/11/1970 (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - Questionnaire, John Robbins, 7/1973 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - A Report From PPFA, Significant PP Accomplishments in USA, 1972, JCR, 9/19/1973-11/11/1973 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - IPPF-WHR-PPFA Financial Arrangements, 1/1973-11/9/1973 (Box 90, Folder 6)
      - IRS Regulations for Contributions Abroad, 1/15/1965-10/23/1970 (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - Restructuring of the IPPF Secretariat, 1/14/1981 (Box 90, Folder 8)
      - Development of the FP Movement in Western Hemisphere History, 2/1967 (Box 90, Folder 9)
      - Lippes Loops, Licensing, Correspondence, 12/18/1964-2/17/1966 (Box 90, Folder 10)
      - Lists, Events, Reports from 1971
        - 1969-1974 (Box 90, Folder 11)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 90)
      - Lists, Events, Reports, 2/23/1967-10/16/1969 (Box 90, Folder 12)
      - New Secretary, General and Reorganization of WHR, 7/10/1964-1/1966 (Box 90, Folder 13)
      - Chimbote Project, 3/23/1971-8/30/1973 (Box 90, Folder 14)
      - Colombian Rural Project, 8/6/1973-8/29/1973 (Box 90, Folder 15)
      - Proposed Reorganization of IPPF-WHR, 9/14/1971-10/12/1971 (Box 90, Folder 16)
      - Regional Council Meeting, Cuernavaca, Mexico, 10/3/1969-12/23/1969 (Box 90, Folder 17)
      - Status for Federal Income Tax Purposes, IRS Sections 501(c)(3), 11/8/1971-11/16/1971 (Box 90, Folder 18)
      - Barbados April 19-23, 1961 3rd Regional Conference, W.I., 4/4/1961-8/8/1961 (Box 90, Folder 19)
      - "World Population Emergency Campaign", Princeton, NJ, 5/20/1959-10/5/1967 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Due to it's large size, the SERIES II container list is divided into two parts. Go to Part 1.